[{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664148728,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":12344,"timeElapsed":61235},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664157888,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":9158,"timeElapsed":70395},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664172024,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":14135,"timeElapsed":84531},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664178858,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":6833,"timeElapsed":91365},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664186463,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":7604,"timeElapsed":98970},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664191224,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4760,"timeElapsed":103731},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664196704,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":5478,"timeElapsed":109211},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664202086,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":5381,"timeElapsed":114593},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664209892,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":7805,"timeElapsed":122399},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664224110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":11964,"timeElapsed":136617},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664233388,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":9277,"timeElapsed":145895},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664239874,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":6485,"timeElapsed":152381},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664245119,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":5245,"timeElapsed":157626},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664251755,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":6635,"timeElapsed":164262},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664257446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5689,"timeElapsed":169953},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664264951,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":7505,"timeElapsed":177458},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664268991,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4039,"timeElapsed":181498},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664272283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3292,"timeElapsed":184790},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664306632,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":32703,"timeElapsed":219139},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664385446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":78813,"timeElapsed":297953},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664390106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":4659,"timeElapsed":302613},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664399675,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":9569,"timeElapsed":312182},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664407044,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":7368,"timeElapsed":319551},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664413458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":6413,"timeElapsed":325965},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664418623,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":5164,"timeElapsed":331130},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664421888,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3264,"timeElapsed":334395},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664425864,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":3974,"timeElapsed":338370},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664436591,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":6771,"timeElapsed":349098},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664443283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":6691,"timeElapsed":355790},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664450472,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":7189,"timeElapsed":362979},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664454939,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4466,"timeElapsed":367446},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664459581,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4640,"timeElapsed":372087},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664468326,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":8745,"timeElapsed":380833},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664471803,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":3476,"timeElapsed":384310},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664474846,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3041,"timeElapsed":387353},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664479707,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":4860,"timeElapsed":392214},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664492328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":11108,"timeElapsed":404835},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664497998,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":5669,"timeElapsed":410505},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664503770,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":5771,"timeElapsed":416277},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664510562,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":6791,"timeElapsed":423069},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664522514,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":11950,"timeElapsed":435021},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664527248,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4733,"timeElapsed":439755},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664530874,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3626,"timeElapsed":443381},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664533850,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2974,"timeElapsed":446357},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664536683,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2832,"timeElapsed":449190},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664548525,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":10286,"timeElapsed":461032},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664552778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4251,"timeElapsed":465285},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664559539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":6760,"timeElapsed":472046},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664564470,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4931,"timeElapsed":476977},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664568414,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3942,"timeElapsed":480920},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664571462,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3047,"timeElapsed":483969},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664574765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3302,"timeElapsed":487272},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664578921,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4155,"timeElapsed":491428},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664581560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"229","question":"Do you have a favorite memory of a sunset? Describe where and when this occurred.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2638,"timeElapsed":494067},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664590799,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":7738,"timeElapsed":503306},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664595245,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":4445,"timeElapsed":507751},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664601144,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5899,"timeElapsed":513651},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664606956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":5811,"timeElapsed":519463},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664610946,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3989,"timeElapsed":523453},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664615142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4195,"timeElapsed":527649},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664617660,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2517,"timeElapsed":530167},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664621408,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3747,"timeElapsed":533915},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664625102,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3693,"timeElapsed":537609},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664628411,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3308,"timeElapsed":540918},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664643002,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":11476,"timeElapsed":555509},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664646781,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3777,"timeElapsed":559288},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664651032,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4250,"timeElapsed":563539},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664656187,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5154,"timeElapsed":568694},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664663431,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7243,"timeElapsed":575938},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664673444,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":10013,"timeElapsed":585951},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664680883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":7430,"timeElapsed":593390},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664685266,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":4378,"timeElapsed":597773},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664688890,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3621,"timeElapsed":601397},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664693850,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":4957,"timeElapsed":606357},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664705330,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":9934,"timeElapsed":617837},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664709365,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4033,"timeElapsed":621872},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664713997,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4630,"timeElapsed":626504},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664719899,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":5900,"timeElapsed":632406},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664731884,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":11984,"timeElapsed":644391},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664735943,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":4057,"timeElapsed":648450},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664739848,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3905,"timeElapsed":652355},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664742632,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2782,"timeElapsed":655139},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664745607,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2975,"timeElapsed":658114},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664755205,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":7030,"timeElapsed":667712},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664759258,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4052,"timeElapsed":671765},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664776628,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":17368,"timeElapsed":689135},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664780972,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":4343,"timeElapsed":693479},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664785310,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":4337,"timeElapsed":697817},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664789093,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":3782,"timeElapsed":701600},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664792930,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3836,"timeElapsed":705437},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664796038,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":3107,"timeElapsed":708545},{"subjectID":"q8xaf46vwx","prolificID":"66de29b7d4d6dd25c97445d1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421546afd1f42dbedf9e2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664798876,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2837,"timeElapsed":711383}]